Guide to the Voices of Contemporary Art Records MSS.601
Fales Library and Special Collections
Voices in Contemporary Art Records
2013-2019
Fales Library and Special Collections
Voices in Contemporary Art
MSS.601
1644 Gigabytes on 4,424 computer files
Voices in Contemporary Art (VoCA) is a non-profit organization devoted to "critical dialogue and interdisciplinary programming to address the production, presentation, and preservation of contemporary art." VoCA's primary programs include workshops, the VoCA Talks series, and VoCA Journal. The Voices in Contemporary Art Records (dated 2013-2019) consist of electronic documents and recordings from the organization's VoCA Talks series of artists discussing various aspects related to the creation, showing, and preservation of contemporary art. Materials in this collection include pdfs, jpegs, and mov files documenting each event, including photographs, promotional materials, transcripts, video recordings, and administrative documents. Event speakers documented in this collection include Henrietta Mantooth, Mimi Smith, Arlan Huang, Jaime Davidovich, Otto Neals, Blane De St.Croix, Juan Sanchez, Christy Rupp, Sarah Oppenheimer, De Wain Valentine, Leonardo Drew, Sonia Almeida, Derrick Adams, Lorraine O'Grady, Tara Sabharwal, Emmett Wigglesworth, Marcos Dimas, Ted Kurahara, Marie Watt, Tory Fair, Gwen Fabricant, Mario Martinez, and Vito Acconci. The collection also includes overall information on the Talks series, including a workflow document, description, release form, and presentation template.
Scope and Contents
The Voices in Contemporary Art Records (dated 2013-2019) consist of electronic documents and recordings from the organization's VoCA Talks series of artists discussing various aspects related to the creation, showing, and preservation of contemporary art. Materials in this collection include pdfs, jpegs, and mov files documenting each event, including photographs, promotional materials, transcripts of remarks, video recordings, and administrative documents. Not every artist who has participated in the VoCA Talks series is represented in this collection. Event speakers documented in this collection include Henrietta Mantooth, Mimi Smith, Arlan Huang, Jaime Davidovich, Otto Neals, Blane De St.Croix, Juan Sanchez, Christy Rupp, Sarah Oppenheimer, De Wain Valentine, Leonardo Drew, Sonia Almeida, Derrick Adams, Lorraine O'Grady, Tara Sabharwal, Emmett Wigglesworth, Marcos Dimas, Ted Kurahara, Marie Watt, Tory Fair, Gwen Fabricant, Mario Martinez, and Vito Acconci. The collection also includes overall information on the Talks series, including a workflow document, description, release form, and presentation template.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged in alphabetic order by the artists' first name, maintaining the order in which they were received from the donor.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Lauren Shadford and Margaret Graham on behalf of Voices in Contemporary Art in February 2020; the accession number associated with this gift is 2020.032.
Born-Digital Access Policies and Procedures
Advance notice is required for the use of computer records. Original physical digital media is restricted. An access terminal for born-digital materials in the collection is available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Researchers may view an item's original container and/or carrier, but the physical carriers themselves are not available for use because of preservation concerns.
Historical Note
Voices in Contemporary Art (VoCA) is a non-profit organization devoted to "critical dialogue and interdisciplinary programming to address the production, presentation, and preservation of contemporary art." VoCA's primary programs include workshops, the VoCA Talks series, and VoCA Journal. VoCA's community includes artists, conservators, curators, art collectors, educators, and students.
Art, Modern -- 21st century.; Art -- Social aspects.; Artists and art museum curators; Voices in Contemporary Art; Huang, Arlan; Rupp, Christy, 1949-; Davidovich, Jaime, 1936-2016; Sanchez, Juan; Acconci, Vito, 1940-; De St. Croix, Blane; Valentine, DeWain, 1936-; Adams, Derrick; Wigglesworth, Emmett, 1939-; Michelson-Bagley, Henrietta, 1934-; Drew, Leonardo; O'Grady, Lorraine; Dimas, Marcos; Watt, Marie, 1967-; Martinez, Mario, 1953-; Smith, Mimi, 1942-; Neals, Otto, 1930-; Oppenheimer, Sarah, 1972-; Almeida, Sonia; Sabharwal, Tara; Kurahara, T.; Fair, Tory; Fabricant, Gwen
- General Information on VoCA Talks Series, 2018-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_1)
- Arlan Huang -- Event Documentation, 2016-2018 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_2)
- Arlan Huang -- Images, 2016-2018 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_3)
- Alan Huang -- Presentation, 2016-2018 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_4)
- Alan Huang -- Promotion, 2016-2018 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_5)
- Alan Huang -- Transcript, 2016-2018 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_6)
- Alan Huang -- Videos, 2016-2018 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_7)
- Blane De St. Croix -- Event Documentation, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_8)
- Blane De St. Croix -- Images, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_9)
- Blane De St. Croix -- Audio, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_10)
- Blane De St. Croix -- Presentation, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_11)
- Blane De St. Croix -- Promotion, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_12)
- Blane De St. Croix -- Transcript, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_13)
- Blane De St. Croix -- Videos, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_14)
- Christy Rupp -- Event Documentation, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_15)
- Christy Rupp -- Images, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_16)
- Christy Rupp -- Presentation, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_17)
- Christy Rupp -- Promotion, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_160)
- Christy Rupp -- Transcript, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_18)
- Christy Rupp -- Videos, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_19)
- De Wain Valentine -- New York -- Event Documentation, 2013-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_20)
- De Wain Valentine -- New York -- Images, 2013-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_21)
- De Wain Valentine -- New York -- Promotion, 2013-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_22)
- De Wain Valentine -- New York -- Transcript, 2013-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_23)
- De Wain Valentine -- New York -- Videos, 2013-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_24)
- De Wain Valentine -- Washington, D.C. -- Event Documentation, 2013-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_25)
- De Wain Valentine -- Washington, D.C. -- Images, 2013-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_26)
- De Wain Valentine -- Washington, D.C. -- Other Materials, 2013-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_27)
- De Wain Valentine -- Washington, D.C. -- Presentation, 2013-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_28)
- De Wain Valentine -- Washington, D.C. -- Promotion, 2013-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_29)
- Derrick Adams -- Event Documentation, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_30)
- Derrick Adams -- Images, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_31)
- Derrick Adams -- Promotion, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_32)
- Derrick Adams -- Transcript, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_33)
- Derrick Adams -- Videos, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_34)
- Emmett Wigglesworth -- Event Documentation, 2016-2018 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_35)
- Emmett Wigglesworth -- Images, 2016-2018 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_36)
- Emmett Wigglesworth -- Presentation, 2016-2018 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_37)
- Emmett Wigglesworth -- Promotion, 2016-2018 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_38)
- Emmett Wigglesworth -- Transcript, 2016-2018 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_39)
- Emmett Wigglesworth -- Videos, 2016-2018 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_40)
- Gwen Fabricant -- Event Documentation, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_41)
- Gwen Fabricant -- Images, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_42)
- Gwen Fabricant -- Other Materials, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_43)
- Gwen Fabricant -- Presentation, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_44)
- Gwen Fabricant -- Promotion, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_45)
- Gwen Fabricant -- Transcript, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_46)
- Gwen Fabricant -- Videos, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_47)
- Henrietta Mantooth -- Event Documentation, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_48)
- Henrietta Mantooth -- Images, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_49)
- Henrietta Mantooth -- Other Materials, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_50)
- Henrietta Mantooth -- Presentation, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_51)
- Henrietta Mantooth -- Promotion, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_52)
- Henrietta Mantooth -- Transcript, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_53)
- Henrietta Mantooth -- Videos, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_54)
- Jaime Davidovich -- Event Documentation, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_55)
- Jaime Davidovich -- Images, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_56)
- Jaime Davidovich -- Other Materials, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_57)
- Jaime Davidovich -- Presentation, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_58)
- Jaime Davidovich -- Promotion, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_59)
- Jaime Davidovich -- Transcript, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_60)
- Jaime Davidovich -- Videos, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_61)
- Juan Sanchez -- Event Documentation, 2015-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_62)
- Juan Sanchez -- Images, 2015-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_63)
- Juan Sanchez -- Presentation, 2015-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_64)
- Juan Sanchez -- Promotion, 2015-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_65)
- Juan Sanchez -- Transcript, 2015-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_66)
- Juan Sanchez -- Videos, 2015-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_67)
- Legacy Specialists -- Event Documentation, 2018-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_68)
- Legacy Specialists -- Images, 2018-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_69)
- Legacy Specialists -- Other Materials, 2018-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_70)
- Legacy Specialists -- Presentation, 2018-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_71)
- Legacy Specialists -- Promotion, 2018-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_72)
- Legacy Specialists -- Transcript, 2018-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_73)
- Legacy Specialists -- Videos, 2018-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_74)
- Leonardo Drew -- Event Documentation, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_75)
- Leonardo Drew -- Images, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_76)
- Leonardo Drew -- Presentation, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_77)
- Leonardo Drew -- Promotion, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_78)
- Leonardo Drew -- Transcript, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_79)
- Leonardo Drew -- Videos, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_80)
- Lorraine O'Grady -- Event Documentation, 2013-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_81)
- Lorraine O'Grady -- Images, 2013-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_82)
- Lorraine O'Grady -- Other Materials, 2013-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_83)
- Lorraine O'Grady -- Promotion, 2013-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_84)
- Lorraine O'Grady -- Transcript, 2013-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_85)
- Lorraine O'Grady -- Videos, 2013-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_86)
- Marcos Dimas -- Event Documentation, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_87)
- Marcos Dimas -- Images, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_88)
- Marcos Dimas -- Presentation, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_89)
- Marcos Dimas -- Promotion, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_90)
- Marcos Dimas -- Transcript, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_91)
- Marcos Dimas -- Videos, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_92)
- Marie Watt -- Event Documentation, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_93)
- Marie Watt -- Images, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_94)
- Marie Watt -- Presentation, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_95)
- Marie Watt -- Promotion, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_96)
- Marie Watt -- Transcript, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_97)
- Marie Watt -- Videos, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_98)
- Mario Martinez -- Event Documentation, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_99)
- Mario Martinez -- Images, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_100)
- Mario Martinez -- Other Documentation, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_101)
- Mario Martinez -- Presentation, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_102)
- Mario Martinez -- Promotion, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_103)
- Mario Martinez -- Transcript, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_104)
- Mario Martinez -- Videos, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_105)
- Mimi Smith -- Event Documentation, 2016-2018 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_106)
- Mimi Smith -- Images, 2016-2018 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_107)
- Mimi Smith -- Other Materials, 2016-2018 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_108)
- Mimi Smith -- Presentation, 2016-2018 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_109)
- Mimi Smith -- Promotion, 2016-2018 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_110)
- Mimi Smith -- Transcript, 2016-2018 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_111)
- Mimi Smith -- Videos, 2016-2018 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_112)
- Otto Neals -- Event Documentation, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_113)
- Otto Neals -- Images, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_114)
- Otto Neals -- Other Materials, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_115)
- Otto Neals -- Promotion, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_116)
- Otto Neals -- Transcript, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_117)
- Otto Neals -- Videos, 2016-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_118)
- Program Partnerships, 2015-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_119)
- Sarah Oppenheimer -- Event Documentation, 2015-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_120)
- Sarah Oppenheimer -- Images, 2015-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_121)
- Sarah Oppenheimer -- Other Materials, 2015-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_122)
- Sarah Oppenheimer -- Presentation, 2015-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_123)
- Sarah Oppenheimer -- Promotion, 2015-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_124)
- Sarah Oppenheimer -- Transcript, 2015-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_125)
- Sarah Oppenheimer -- Videos, 2015-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_126)
- Sonia Almeida -- Event Documentation, 2018-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_127)
- Sonia Almeida -- Images, 2018-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_128)
- Sonia Almeida -- Presentation, 2018-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_129)
- Sonia Almeida -- Promotion, 2018-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_130)
- Sonia Almeida -- Transcript, 2018-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_131)
- Sonia Almeida -- Videos, 2018-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_132)
- Tara Sabharwal -- Event Documentation, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_133)
- Tara Sabharwal -- Images, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_134)
- Tara Sabharwal -- Other Materials, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_135)
- Tara Sabharwal -- Presentation, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_136)
- Tara Sabharwal -- Promotion, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_137)
- Tara Sabharwal -- Transcript, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_138)
- Tara Sabharwal -- Videos, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_139)
- Ted Kurahara -- Event Documentation, 2018-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_140)
- Ted Kurahara -- Images, 2018-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_141)
- Ted Kurahara -- Other Materials, 2018-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_142)
- Ted Kurahara -- Presentation, 2018-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_143)
- Ted Kurahara -- Promotion, 2018-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_144)
- Ted Kurahara -- Transcript, 2018-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_145)
- Ted Kurahara -- Videos, 2018-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_146)
- Tory Fair -- Event Documentation, 2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_147)
- Tory Fair -- Images, 2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_148)
- Tory Fair -- Presentation, 2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_149)
- Tory Fair -- Promotion, 2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_150)
- Tory Fair -- Transcript, 2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_151)
- Tory Fair -- Videos, 2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_152)
- Vito Acconci -- Event Documentation, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_153)
- Vito Acconci -- Images, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_154)
- Vito Acconci -- Other Materials, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_155)
- Vito Acconci -- Presentation, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_156)
- Vito Acconci -- Promotion, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_157)
- Vito Acconci -- Transcript, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_158)
- Vito Acconci -- Videos, 2017-2019 (E-records Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_601_ER_159)